Steven H. Scheuer Publicity Stills Collection
Steven H. Scheuer Publicity Stills Collection
- Photographs
  - Producer's Showcase: The Barretts of Wimpole Street, 4/2/1956; 2470; 7x9, fair/average condition; includes caption; Cornell, Katharine (Box 8)
  - Profiles in Courage: The Mary S. McDowell Story, 1/12/1964; 2233; 9x7, poor condition; includes caption; Harris, Rosemary; Christie, Audrey (Box 8)
  - Profiles in Courage: Thomas Hart Benton, 11/29/1964; 2309; 7x9, excellent condition; includes caption; Keith, Brian (Box 8)
  - Project 20: The Great War, 9/14/1956; 2313; 9x7, fair/average condition; includes caption; World War I (Box 8)
  - Project 20: The Innocent Years, 2189; 7x9, fair/average condition; includes caption; Roosevelt, Theodore; Fourth of July (Box 8)
  - Project 20: The Jazz Age, 2423; 10x8, fair/average condition; includes caption; Jazz musicians; Jazz dancers (Box 8)
  - Projection '58, 12/29/1958; 2615; 7x9, fair/average condition; includes caption; Harsch, Joseph C. (Box 8)
  - Projection '63, 12/14/1962; 2192; 7x9, fair/average condition; includes caption (Box 8)
  - Quincy Howe News Commentary, 1/8/1954; 2535; 7x9, good condition; includes caption; Howe, Quincy (Box 8)
  - Quinn, Carmel, 2220; 8x10, fair/average condition (Box 8)
  - Quinn, Carmel, 2364; 8x10, poor condition (Box 8)
  - R-TV (Radio-TV Daily), 2097; 8x10, fair/average condition
  - R-TV (Radio-TV Daily), 2105; 8x10, fair/average condition
  - RAB (Radio Advertising Bureau), 2099; 9x7, good condition (Box 8)
  - RAB (Radio Advertising Bureau), 2100; 9x7, good condition (Box 8)
  - Ray Milland Show, 7/8/1955; 1996; 8x10, poor condition; includes caption; Avery, Phyllis; Milland, Ray (Box 8)
  - Ray Milland Show, 8/20/1954; 2000; 4x5, fair/average condition; includes caption; Milland, Ray (Box 8)
  - Ray Milland Show, 8/2/1954; 2001; 8x10 2 items, fair/average condition; includes caption; Milland, Ray (Box 8)
  - Ray Milland Show, 11/22/1954; 2002; 4x5, good condition; includes caption; Corrigan, Lloyd (Box 8)
  - RCA, 4/8/1964; 2093; 8x10, good condition; Eubanks, Anita; Colledge, Charles H.; RCA Broadcast and Communications Products; Dick Tracy (Comic strip); Gould, Chester (Box 8)
  - Real McCoys, 2287; 7x9, poor condition; includes caption, depicts Dick Crenna end family and Kathy Nolan relaxing at the beach; Crenna, Dick (Richard); Crenna, Seana; Nolan, Kathy; Crenna, Penni (Box 8)
  - Real McCoys: Grampa Fights the Air Force, 11/26/1959; 2235; 7x9, poor condition; includes caption; Brennan, Walter; Houston, Ann (Box 8)
  - Real McCoys: The New Car, 9/17/1958; 2631; 7x9, good condition; includes caption; Brennan, Walter; Martinez, Tony; Winkelman, Michael; Reed, Lydia; Nolan, Kathy; Crenna, Richard (Box 8)
  - Rebel: Take Dead Aim, 3/6/1960; 2240; 7x9, poor condition; includes caption; Adams, Nick (Box 8)
  - Rebel: Yellow Hair, 10/18/1959; 2580; 7x9, fair/average condition; includes caption; Nugent, Caro (Box 8)
  - Reed, Donna, 2114; 7x9, fair/average condition (Box 8)
  - Remember How Great, 2573; 9x7, good condition; includes caption (Box 8)
  - Renney, Ed, 2026; 8x10, fair/average condition (Box 8)
  - Resources for Freedom, 1/10/1952; 2323; 9x7, very poor condition; includes caption; 8 pictures on sheet; President's Materials Policy Commission; Baruch, Bernard; Paley, William S.; Murrow, Edward R.; Pandit, Vijaya; Bush, Vannevar (Box 8)
  - Rifleman: A Young Man’s Fancy, 2/5/1962; 2288; 7x9, fair/average condition; includes caption; Crawford, Johnny; Holdridge, Cheryl (Box 8)
  - Rifleman: Sharpshooter, 9/2/1958; 1987; 7x9, fair/average condition; includes caption; Connors, Chuck (Box 8)
  - Rivak, the Barbarian, 10/4/1960; 2325; 7x9, excellent condition; includes caption; Vitale, Millie; Mason, F. Van Wyck; Palance, Jack (Box 8)
  - Rivak, the Barbarian, 10/4/1960; 2326; 7x9, excellent condition; includes caption; Mason, F. Van Wyck; Palance, Jack (Box 8)
  - Riverboat: The Two faces of Grey Holden, 10/3/1960; 2502; 7x9, fair/average condition; includes caption; McGavin, Darren; Pleshette, Suzanne (Box 8)
  - Roaring 20s, 2572; 7.5x9, fair/average condition; includes caption; Reason, Rex; Provine, Dorothy; May, Donald (Box 8)
  - Roaring 20s: Two A Day, 1993; 7x9, fair/average condition; includes caption; May, Donald; O'Neill, Eileen (Box 8)
  - Sarnoff and Kintnes, 2095; 6.5x8, poor condition (Box 9)
  - Saturday Night at the Movies: Bird of Paradise, 312/1962; 2363; 7x9, good condition; includes caption; Polynesians; Paget, Debra (Box 9)
  - Saturday Night at the Movies: The Black Rose, 2/9/1962; 2601; 9x7, good condition; includes caption; Hawkins, Jack; Aubry, Cecile (Box 9)
  - Saturday Night Fites, 1957; 7x9, good condition; includes caption; Gregson, Jack; Boxing (Box 9)
  - Say When, 12/16/1960; 1960; 7x9, poor condition; includes caption; James, Art (Box 9)
  - Say When, 2/8/1963; 2301; 7x9, good condition; includes caption; James, Art (Box 9)
  - Schlitz Playhouse of Stars: Bandit's Hide-Out, 10/7/1955; 2177; 8xl0, fair/average condition; includes caption; Quinn, Anthony; Saunders, Gloria (Box 9)
  - Schlitz Playhouse of Stars: For Better, For Worse, 2117; 8x10, fair/average condition; includes caption; Stricklyn, Ray; Williams, John; Davis, Bette (Box 9)
  - Schlitz Playhouse of Stars: Ordeal, 2/24/1956; 1998; 8x6, good condition; includes caption; Ireland, John; Cooper, Maxine (Box 9)
  - Schlitz Playhouse of Stars: Tourists Overnite, 3/25/1955; 2624; 8x10, poor condition; includes caption; Hale, Barbara; Murphy, Donald (Box 9)
  - Schlitz Playhouse of Stars: Weapon of Courage, 6/29/1956; 2005; 7x9, extremely poor condition; includes caption; McCarthy, Kevin; Cooper, Maxine; Winkleman, Michael (Box 9)
  - Schriner, Herb, 2086; 8x10, good condition (Box 9)
  - Screen Directors Playhouse: Partners, 6/14/1956; 2282; 7x9, fair/average condition; includes caption; de Wilde, Brandon (Box 9)
  - Screen Gems, 2100; 8x10, good condition; Mitchell, John H. (Box 9)
  - Senor Ben (Radio program), 1981; 7x9, fair/average condition; includes caption; NBC Radio; Grauer, Ben (Box 9)
  - Sermon on the Mount, and The Passion and the Resurrection, 3/4/1959; 2647; 9x7, fair/average condition; includes caption; Painters, French; Girard, Andre; National Council of Catholic Men (Box 9)
  - SESAC, 2084; 10x8, good condition; Heinecke, Paul; Koshel, John; SESAC; Drusky, Roy (Box 9)
  - Sesame Street, March 1988; 1480; 7x5, excellent condition; PBS Television Network; Placido Flamingo; Ozawa, Seiji (Box 9)
  - Sesame Street, March 1988; 1482; 5x7, excellent condition; Anita and Steve Shevet, photographers; Irons, Jeremy; Big Bird (Fictitious character); PBS Television Network (Box 9)
  - Shake, Rattle, and Roll, 1504; 10x8, excellent condition; Don Perdue, photographer;2 photographs on sheet; Lewis, Jerry Lee; Rock music; PBS Television Network; Checker, Chubby (Box 9)
  - Shari Lewis Show, 9/8/1962; 2296; 7x9, good condition; includes caption; Lewis, Shari; Jump Pup (Fictitious character) (Box 9)
  - Sherlock Holmes: Case of the Cunningham Heritage, 10/18/1954; 2509; 8x10, poor condition; includes caption; Howard, Ronald (Box 9)
  - Shirley Temple Show: Little Men, 10/7/1960; 2271; 7x9, poor condition; includes caption; Temple, Shirley; Lamas, Fernando (Box 9)
  - Shirley Temple Show: The Fawn, 2/12/1960; 2465; 9x7, fair/average condition; includes caption; Crawford, Robert, Jr. (Box 9)
  - Shirley Temple's Storybook: Rip Van Winkle, 2275; 7x9, poor condition; includes caption; Dana, Leora; Washburn, Beverly (Box 9)
  - Shirley Temple's Storybook: The Nightingale, 2/19/1958; 2472; 7x9, fair/average condition; includes caption; Braun, Judith (Box 9)
  - Shower of Stars: A Christmas Carol, 11/18/1954; 2471; 7x9, fair/average condition; includes caption; Dickens, Charles; Anderson, Maxwell; March, Frederic (Box 9)
  - Silents Please: The General, 8/11/1960; 2310; 9x7; includes caption; Keaton, Buster (Box 9)
  - Sing Along with Mitch, 1966; 8x10, good condition; includes caption; Miller, Mitch; Lamon, Barbara; Bravo, Veronica; Mattis, Dee Jay; Ryhal, Mary Lou (Box 9)
  - Singer Four Star Playhouse: Girl on a Park Bench, 5/12/1954; 2332; 8x10; includes caption; Fontaine, Joan (Box 9)
  - Singers, 2642; 8x10, poor condition; Como, Perry; Page, Patti (Box 9)
  - Soldier Parade, 2204; 8x10, fair/average condition; includes caption; Armbrust, Richard; Francis, Arlene (Box 9)
  - Split Personality (game show), 9/28/1959; 2515; 9x7, good condition; includes caption (Box 9)
  - Sports International with Bud Palmer, 1/18/1963; 2408; 7x9, very poor condition; includes caption; Palmer, Bud (Box 9)
  - Stark, Art, 2560; 5x7, poor condition (Box 9)
  - Steve Allen Show, 4/4/1958; 2519; 7x9, good condition; includes caption; 4 images on sheet; Jameson, Joyce (Box 9)
  - Straightaway: Sounds of Fury, 2170; 7x9, poor condition; includes caption; Moore, Mary Tyler (Box 9)
  - Stroke of Fate, 10/2/1953; 2475; 9x7, good condition; includes caption; Lorant, Stefan; Lewis, Mort (Box 9)
  - Studio One: Side Street, 2/7/1954; 2610; 7x9; includes caption; Healy, Mary; Hayes, Peter Lind (Box 9)
  - Sugar Bowl / l975, 1/1/1955; 7x9, poor condition; includes caption; Monahan, Phil (Box 9)
  - Sugarfoot: Shepherd with a Gun, 7/24/1961; 2541; 7x9, fair/average condition; includes caption; Hadley, Nancy; (Box 9)
  - Sugarfoot: The Corsican, 2214; 7x9, good condition; includes caption; Hutchins, Will; Powers, Nala (Box 9)
  - Summer Variety Show, 2638; 7x9, fair/average condition; includes caption; Page, Patti (Box 9)
  - Sunday Showcase: Give My Regards to Broadway, 2527; 9x7, good condition; includes caption; Durante, Jimmy; Bolger, Ray; Powell, Jane (Box 9)
  - Sunday Showcase: Murder and the Android, 11/8/1959; 2501; 9x7, good condition; includes caption; Osato, Sono; Bester, Alfred; Torn, Rip; Pleshette, Suzanne; McCarthy, Kevin (Box 9)
  - Surfside 6: Ghost of a Chance, 3/6/1961; 2272; 7x9, poor condition; includes caption; Kelly, Claire; Williams, Van (Box 9)
  - Suspicion: Lord Arthur Savile's Crime, 1/13/1958; 2622; 7x9, good condition; includes caption; Howard, Ronald; Harris, Rosemary (Box 9)
  - Swan, 1528; 10x8, excellent condition; Guinness, Alec; Kelly, Grace; PBS Television Network (Box 9)
  - Swan, Ruth, 2050; 8x10, extremely poor condition (Box 9)
  - Swing Into Spring, 2444; 9x7, poor condition; includes caption; Goodman, Benny (Box 9)
  - Sword of Islam, 1/12/1988; 1512; 10x8, excellent condition; Palestine; PBS Television Network (Box 9)
  - Sylvania Electric Products Inc., 3/25/1964; 2082; 8x10, good condition; includes article about computer to display airport arrival and departure times; General Telephone & Electronics Corporation (GTE); Computers--History (Box 9)
  - Talking with David Frost, 11/22/1991; 4374; 10x8, excellent condition; John, Elton (Box 9)
  - Tall Man: The Judas Palm, 2259; 9x7, good condition; includes caption; Gulager, Clu; Hill, Marianna; Buchanan, Edgar (Box 9)
  - Telephone Time: War Against War, 1969; 7x9, good condition; includes caption; Tandy, Jessica; Cronyn, Hume (Box 9)
  - Television, 1/25/1988; 1494; 5x7, excellent condition; Newman, Edward; PBS Television Network (Box 9)
  - This Honorable Court, 3/21/1988; 1524; l0x8, excellent condition; Joan Marcus, photographer; 2 photographs on sheet; White, Byron; Duke, Paul; Supreme Court (U.S.); PBS Television Network (Box 9)
  - This is Your Life, 7/10/1959; 2476; 7x9, good condition; includes caption; Edwards, Ralph; Lewis, Ted (Box 9)
  - Those Whiting Girls, 8117/1955; 2249; 8x10, fair/average condition; includes caption; 2 photos on sheet; Hadley with long hair and with short hair; Hadley, Nancey (Box 9)
  - Tic Tac Dough, 1984; 4.5x7, fair/average condition; includes caption; Elliot, Win (Box 9)
  - Today on the Farm, 2479; 7x9, fair/average condition; includes caption; Pope, Carmelite; Arnold, Eddy (Box 9)
  - Tomorrow (Tomorrow's Careers), 2369; 8x10, good condition; includes caption; Poole, Lynn (Box 9)
  - Tonight, 11/15/1957; 1980; 7x9, fair/average condition; includes caption; Mitchell, Joan (Box 9)
  - Tonight, 4/20/1955; 2284; 9x7, poor condition; includes caption; Benny Goodman Story (Motion picture); Allen, Steve; Goodman, Benny (Box 9)
  - Tony Martin Show, 1971; 8x10, good condition; includes caption; Martin, Tony; Charisse, Cyd (Box 9)
  - Topper, 5/13/1956; 2012; 9x7, fair/average condition; includes caption; Jeffreys, Anne; Carroll, Leo G.; Sterling, Robert (Box 9)
  - Tournament of Champions, 1992; 7x9, good condition; includes caption; Holt, Charlene; Golf (Box 9)
  - TV Hour: Outlaw’s Reckoning, 10/26/1953; 2382; 7x9, very poor condition; includes caption; Albert, Eddie; Marvin, Lee; Cummings, Vicki (Box 9)
  - TV Reader's Digest: France's Great Detective, 5/10/1955; 2653; 8x10, fair/average condition; includes caption; Patrick, Millicent; Franz, Arthur (Box 9)
  - TvAR (Television Advertising Report), 2096; 10x8 (Box 9)
  - United States Steel Hour, 2365; 8x10, fair/average condition; includes caption; Proesel, Marion Ellen; Interior designers (Box 9)
  - United States Steel Hour: The Meanest Man in the World, 6/17/1955; 2225; 7x9, fair/average condition; includes caption; Cox, Wally; Hull, Josephine; Delmar, Kenny (Box 9)
  - Untouchables: The Doreen Maney Story, 8/4/1960; 2584; 7x9, fair/average condition; includes caption; Hines, Connie (Box 9)
  - Untouchables: The Rusty Heller Story, 10/13/1960; 2633; 7x9, poor condition; includes caption; Walkins, Linda; Montgomery, Elizabeth (Box 9)
  - Valiant Lady, 2207; 7x9, good condition; includes caption; Sawyer, Bonnie; Coleman, Nancy (Box 10)
  - VA-TV Execs, 3/27/1964; 2091; 10x8, fair/average condition (Box 10)
  - Vera-Ellen (Rohe, Vera-Ellen Westmeyer), 2406; 9x7, poor condition; includes caption (Box 10)
  - Vise: Cross Channel, 10/21/1955; 2429; 10x8, very poor condition; includes caption; Holt, Patrick; Connell, Maureen (Box 10)
  - Vise: Let Murder Be Done, 10/15/1954; 2252; 9x7, fair/average condition; includes caption; Scott, Avis; Price, Dennis (Box 10)
  - Vise: The Better Chance, 6/24/1955; 2453; 8x10, very poor condition; includes caption; Callard, Kay; Phillips, Leslie (Box 10)
  - Voice of Firestone, 1976; 7x9, extremely poor condition; includes caption; Hines, Jerome; Evangelista, Lucia (Box 10)
  - Voice of Firestone, 2199; 7x9, fair/average condition; includes caption; Munsel, Patrice (Box 10)
  - Voice of Firestone, 2200; 8x10, fair/average condition; includes caption; Munsel, Patrice (Box 10)
  - Voices and Visions, 1/26/1988; 1498; 8x10, excellent condition; PBS Television Network; Moore, Marianne; Frost, Robert; Poets, American (Box 10)
  - Wagon Train: Stagecoach Story, 9/30/1960; 2311; 7x9, fair/average condition; includes caption; Paget, Debra (Box 10)
  - Wagon Train: The John Augustus Story, 10/17/1962; 2293; 7x9, fair/average condition; includes caption; Cotten, Joseph (Box 10)
  - Wagon Train: The Les Rand Story, 9/30/1957; 2602; 8x10, good condition; includes caption; Hayden, Sterling (Box 10)
  - Walt Disney Presents: Killers from Kansas, 1/9/1959; 2265; 8x10, poor condition; includes caption; Bettger, Lyle; Garland, Beverly; Tryon, Tom (Box 10)
  - Walt Disney Presents: The Swamp Fox, 10/23/1959; 2482; 7x9, fair/average condition; includes caption; Nielson, Sandy; Nielson, Leslie (Box 10)
  - Walt Disney's Wonderful World of Color: Treasure Island, 1/5/1955; 2202; 7x9, fair/average condition; includes caption; Driscoll, Bobby; Stevenson, Robert Louis (Box 10)
  - Warner Brothers Presents: Casablanca, 9/27/1955; 2352; 8x10, very poor condition; includes caption; Muse, Clarence (Box 10)
  - Warner Brothers Presents: Siege, 2/14/1956; 2489; 8x10, fair/average condition; includes caption; Richards, Paul (Box 10)
  - Watch Mr. Wizard, 2495; 9x7, fair/average condition; includes caption; Fox, Phil; Herbert, Don (Box 10)
  - WBAP, WFM, and KRLD, 2029; 8x10, good condition; includes caption; Johnson, J. Lee; Moroney, James M.; Rembert, Clyde W.; WBAP-TV (Television station); WFM-TV (Television station); KRLD-TV (Television station); Cedar Hills (Tx) (Box 10)
  - Wendy (Elephant), 2374; 8x10, very poor condition; Wendelken, George (Box 10)
  - Westinghouse Desilu Playhouse: Six Guns for Donegan, 10/16/1958; 2357; 8x10, poor condition; includes caption; Hagen, Jean (Box 10)
  - Westinghouse Studio One: The Landlady's Daughter, 11/19/1959; 2308; 10x8, good condition; includes caption; Matthews, George; Kiley, Richard; Remick, Lee (Box 10)
  - What's Going On? (game show), 11/28/1952; 2443; 8x10, fair/average condition; includes caption; Norton, Cliff (Box 10)
  - What's My Line (game show), 10/22/1953; 2538; 10x8, very poor condition; includes caption; Cerf, Bennett; Kilgallen, Dorothy; Daly, John; Francis, Alene; Allen, Steve (Box 10)
  - Who Cares for the Children?, 4/13/1988; 1521; 8x10, excellent condition; Perlman, Rhea; PBS Television Network (Box 10)
  - Who Lives, Who Dies, 1/5/1988; 1490; 7.5x5, excellent condition; PBS Television Network; Jones, James Earl (Box 10)
  - Wide Country, 2179; 7x9, good condition; includes caption; Doucette, John; Prine, Andrew (Box 10)
  - Wild America: Beautiful Blues, Swamp Bear, Timberdoodles of Moosehorn, 1509; 10x8, excellent condition; 3 photographs on sheet; PBS Television Network (Box 10)
  - WISH-TV, 5/6/1964; 2089; 8x10, good condition; S & H Green stamps; McConnell, Robert B.; Klaubes, Donald; Seven Arts; WISH-TV (Indianapolis, IN) (Box 10)
  - WNEW Radio, 2047; 8x10, good condition; Karl Weyner, photographer; Finch, Dee; Klavan, Gene; WNEW (Radio station) (Box 10)
  - Wonderworks, 1/2/1988; 1510; 8x10, excellent condition; 2 photographs on sheet; Grimes, Scott; Gould, Elliot; Duvall, Shelley; PBS Television Network (Box 10)
  - World of Bob Hope, 6/21/1963; 2413; 7x9, fair/average condition; includes caption; Golf; Hope, Bob (Box 10)
  - World of Maurice Chevalier, 2120; 7x9, fair/average condition; includes caption (Box 10)
  - WWDC Conference, 2076; 10x8, good condition; Washington Radio Board (Box 10)
  - You Don't Say (game show), 12/13/1963; 2582; 7x9, good condition; includes caption; Jewell, Carol; Kennedy, Tom (Box 10)
  - You Don't Say, 3/8/1963; 2290; 7x9, fair/average condition; includes caption; Kennedy, Tom (Box 10)
  - Young Widder Brown (Radio program), 2341; 7x9, poor condition; includes caption; NBC Radio; Drew, Wendy (Box 10)
  - Your Hit Parade, 2292; 9x7, poor condition; includes caption; 4 pictures on sheet; Gibson, Virginia (Box 10)
  - Your Hit Parade, 2415; 7x9, good condition; includes caption; Lanson, Snooky; MacKenzie, Giselle; Arms, Russell; Collins, Dorothy (Box 10)
  - Your Hit Parade, 2437; 9x7, fair/average condition; includes caption; Copeland, Alan; Gibson, Virginia; Leonelli, Tommy; Corey, Jill (Box 10)
  - Yours for a Song (game show), 2396; 7x9, good condition; includes caption; Parks, Bert (Box 10)
  - Unidentified, 2129 through; varying in size and condition; cannot locate these at the moment; 127 items